http://www.doccafe.com/terms

Call us now:
Back to Top
It is the goal of DocCafe.com to provide accessible, secure services to our customers while guaranteeing that your information is protected.
Terms
"Candidate" means a User who is accessing a Site to search for a job or in any other capacity except as an Employer/Recruiter.
"Content" includes all Text, Graphics, Design and Programming used on the Sites.
"Design" includes the color combinations and the page layout of the Sites.
"Document" refers to any posting to a Site, whether job or resume.
"Employer" means a person or entity that is accessing a Site to post a job or utilizing the Services for any reason related to the purpose of seeking candidates for employment.
"Employer Materials" includes any brochures, emails, sample job postings, web site content, career fair material, audio, videos, photographs, logos, trademarks, service marks, domain names, documents or other materials provided by Employer, if any, for use in connection with the Services.
"Graphics" includes all logos, buttons, and other graphical elements on the Sites, with the exception of paid advertising banners.
"Materials" includes any materials, methodologies, implementation plans or other intellectual property used during the provision of Services. "DocCafe.Com, LLC Web Site" means any web site under DocCafe.Com, LLC control, whether partial or otherwise and includes such Site's Content, Text, Graphics, Design, Programming, Materials and Services (as applicable in each context).
"Programming" includes both client-side code (HTML, JavaScript, etc.) and server-side code (Active Server Pages, VBScript, databases, etc.) used on the Sites.
"Services" means any services provided by or its agents described herein and specified more fully in the Distribution and Service Provision Agreement.
"Text" includes all text on every page of the Sites, whether editorial, navigational, or instructional.
"User" refers to any individual or entity that uses any aspect of the Sites.
"You" or "you" means the person who (or the entity on behalf of whom you are acting) that is agreeing to these Terms and Conditions.
"Web Site" means any web site under DocCafe.Com, LLC control, whether partial or otherwise and includes such Site's Content, Text, Graphics, Design, Programming, Materials and Services (as applicable in each context).
Disclaimer
Abuse Prevention Policy
DocCafe.Com, LLC has the ability to research, track and monitor all user activities and interactions on the DocCafe.Com, LLC web site in order to promote a secure online environment. DocCafe.Com, LLC attempts to provide Job Seekers protection against online scammers through education on scams and proactive investigation. DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to review and verify company job postings, job seeker registrations, emails sent by company employees and administrators as well as emails sent by registered job seekers. DocCafe.Com, LLC enforces the website Terms and Conditions and will take all necessary action required to prevent abuse of the DocCafe.Com, LLC system.
Any company, employee or job seeker found to be violating the Terms and Conditions of the DocCafe.Com, LLC website or to be found by the company to be engaged in fraudulent or inappropriate use will be terminated from the website and monetary damages may be assessed by the company for reinstatement or as appropriate compensation depending on the found misuse. DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to file civil suits for damages if the situation warrants. DocCafe.Com, LLC will respond to a court order or subpoena request for records and/or information regarding any individual or company use of the web site.
In the event that you have any concerns regarding fraudulent or inappropriate use of the DocCafe.Com, LLC site, please contact us at contact@doccafe.com.
Terms of Use/Acceptable Use Policy
YOUR USE OF THIS SITE REPRESENTS YOUR ACCEPTANCE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OUTLINED IN EACH OF THE POLICIES AND PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OR YOU DO NOT MEET OR COMPLY WITH THEM, YOU ARE NOT ABLE TO USE THE DocCafe.com SITE OR SERVICES. THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ARE EFFECTIVE AS OF APRIL 25, 2019.
This site's function is to put Job Seekers who are looking for an employment opportunity in touch with hospitals, private practice groups or recruiters that are looking to fill an employment opportunity as well as to provide professional information and networking to all types of users. We maintain the Site as a service to its visitors and users subject to the following terms and conditions. When you use the Site, you accept the Terms of Use and agree to be bound by the full terms set forth below. If you do not agree with the Terms of Use you may not use the Site. We reserve the right to modify content on the Site and these Terms of Use periodically without prior notice. Any additional terms of disclaimer that are displayed under the disclaimer heading of this site are incorporated and made a part of this agreement. You are also agreeing to use the Sites at your own risk.
EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED IN ANY OUTSIDE AGREEMENT THAT YOU MAY HAVE WITH THIS SITE, ALL CONTENT AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR THE APPROPRIATENESS OF THE CONTENT THAT YOU PLACE ON THE SITE AND FOR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF ANY CONTENT THAT YOU TAKE OFF OF THE SITE. THIS SITE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY THIS SITE MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, SUBJECT TO THE TERMS OF ANY OUTSIDE AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND THE SITE. THIS SITE/COMPANY NOR ITS AGENTS, CONTRACTORS, ATTORNEYS, STOCKHOLDERS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, EVEN IF THIS SITE/COMPANY OR ITS CONTRACTORS, ATTORNEYS, STOCKHOLDERS OR EMPLOYEES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBLITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS SITE/COMPANY DISCLAIMS ALL RESPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES AND/OR AGREEMENTS THAT YOU MAY MAKE WITH THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS, HYPERLINKS OR POSTERS OF THE SITE. IN THE EVENT THAT STATE LAW DOES NOT ALLOW THE ABOVE STATED LIMITATIONS, THE ABOVE DISCLAIMER SHALL APPLY TO THE EXTENT ALLOWABLE BY STATE LAW.
Use of Content on the Site
You may view, download and print contents from the Site subject to the following conditions:
A. The content must be used solely for the purpose of finding employment or finding a candidate to fill an employment opportunity or to provide professional or professional networking information to the other users of the web site.
B. The content cannot be modified or altered in any way.
C. The content cannot be republished, distributed or used in any manner other than what is explicitly permitted herein.
D. You are not allowed to use any logo, trademark, image or video piece taken from this website without express written permission from us.
E. Any unauthorized use terminates your right to utilize this site.
F. Any unauthorized use may result in an assessment of damages.
G. You may post positions and CVs on this site but are not allowed to submit any content that is obscene, illegal, threatening or defamatory and you are not allowed to invade the privacy of a third party with any information taken from this site.
H. You are not allowed to use a false e-mail address or impersonate any person or entity, or provide any information that is misleading. Such action will result in removal from the web site.
I. By submitting information you represent that the content is accurate, current, reliable, complete and error-free.
J. You agree that we may terminate without refund a user’s ability to post on this site should it be determined that the user has violated this agreement.
K. You agree that we may assess damages for any loss of income or actual or implied damages that may result from your misuse, abuse or fraudulent behavior on this web site.
L. We do not guarantee that the information posted to this site is true and accurate information. Each recruiter, hospital or agency is responsible for conducting its own reference and CV investigation to determine the validity of the posters information. Each candidate is responsible for gathering its own information regarding a position posting prior to entering into any agreement with a recruiter, hospital or other health care provider.
Trademark and Copyright information
We respect the intellectual property of others. Please respect ours. The Site and contents within the Site are the property of DocCafe.Com, LLC and is protected by the United States Copyright laws. The compilation, organization and display of this Site are the exclusive property of DocCafe.Com, LLC. We reserve all rights to this Site and its content even if it is not specifically granted in any agreements with Us or in the Terms of Use. DocCafe.Com, LLC designs that are marked indicate that they are registered trademarks. Other designs, marks, graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts noted on the Site are the sole and exclusive property of this Site and are not able to be used in any manner that may cause confusion with customers, in any manner that disparages or discredits this site or our Company and in connection with any service that is not sponsored, endorsed or produced by this site or our Company. All other trademarks that are not owned by this site but that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners.
NonSolicitation
No user may use the information posted onto this site to solicit others to use or invest in competing products, services or companies. Such activity is a violation of this Agreement and such user/s will be terminated and monetary damages may be accessed for any unlicensed and/or unauthorized use.
Privacy Policy
We respect your right to privacy and for that reason we have developed a privacy policy. Please view that policy on this site on a regular basis so that you are aware of our protections and practices. The privacy policy and its terms are on this site under the icon, "Privacy Policy". The Privacy Policy is incorporated and made a part of this agreement. Click here to view Privacy Policy
Terms of Use for Blog and Resource Section
To assist with professional development and professional associations, DocCafe.Com, LLC provides a professional development article, blog and posting system. All Users, will have access to the blog and resource section of the website and therefore need to accept responsibility for any postings and comments that an individual or company posts on that section. You agree to accepting this General Terms and Use and by your one time or repeated use of this website.
Any information read or acted upon that is found in part or in entirety on this blog are subject to the terms of use. All users are reading the blog materials of their own free will. Any recommendations, links or content is the user’s personal choice and any subsequent action is done so at your own risk. Unless otherwise noted, DocCafe.com LLC is the copyright holder of all content appearing on the site. You may not republish, reprint or reuse content without our expressed written consent.
All content provided is for informational purposes only. We do not provide medical or legal advice. Any recommendations or states are based on opinion and any actions taken are of your own free will. Should you chose to take action based on the content read on this site, you do so at your own risk and agree to hold DocCafe.com harmless.
Comments are welcomed and encouraged on this site, but there are instances where comments will be edited or deleted as follows:
Comments deemed to be spam or solely promotional in nature will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted but comments should be relevant to the post topic. If they are deemed not relevant, they will be removed.
Comments including profanity will be deleted.
Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive will be deleted. Note this may include abusive, threatening, pornographic, offensive, misleading or libelous language.
Comments that attack an individual directly will be deleted.
Comments that harass other posters will be deleted. Please be respectful toward other contributors.
Anonymous comments will be deleted. We only accept comments from posters who identify themselves.
DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to edit or delete any comments submitted to the blog without notice. This comment policy is subject to change at any time.
License to Use by Users who are Candidates
DocCafe.Com, LLC hereby grants you a nonexclusive, limited, terminable right to access and use the Sites only for your personal use to pursue employment opportunities and additional career information. This license authorizes you to view and make one personal copy of any posting for jobs in your occupation and preference. You agree that you are the only person responsible for posting your personal information to this site and any consequences as a result of such posting is your sole responsibility. DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to suspend or terminate your site usage for any reason, at any time and in its sole discretion.
License to Use by Users who are Employers or Recruiters
DocCafe.Com, LLC hereby grants you a nonexclusive, limited, terminable, right to access and post on the sites for your professional purpose of obtaining employees directly for your company or a company that you directly represent. As a recruiter, your company must have a contract directly with a healthcare employer to post their job/s for the sole purpose of sourcing and placing candidates directly with such employer per the terms of the contract. Compensation from employers to recruiters must be associated with hires that have resulted from that direct job seeker presentation. Marketing companies or Media companies do not qualify as recruiting agencies for this purpose. Companies that provide an upsell marketing opportunity for a flat fee to employers do not qualify as recruiters for this purpose and are not qualified users of this site. This authorizes employers and recruiters to view and download a single copy of candidate’s material for the sole purpose of possible employment and job prospects. You may not sell, transfer or assign any of the Service or your rights to any of the Services provided by DocCafe.Com, LLC to any third party without the express written authority of DocCafe.Com, LLC. You may also not use your license for any other company or affiliate that your company has acquired, initiated or merged into your existing company without the express written authority of DocCafe.Com, LLC. You agree that you are solely responsible for any material that you post or upload to the site and any consequences arising from such posting.
Recruiters and Employers shall not engage in Applicant Harvesting which is the process of obtaining information (personal, employment or otherwise) about a candidate by using false, fictitious, misleading or alluring job postings to unfairly entice a job seeker to divulge personal, employment or other information that he or she would not divulge if the intent of such a job posting were known by the candidate
You may not respond to postings by other users in any manner or for any purpose other than that which is expected (i.e., to apply for the job or to initiate further discussion with the candidate). Communications soliciting the employer's business are prohibited.
DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to terminate your license at any time in the event that it determines that you are in breach of these Terms and Conditions. DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to assess monetary damages for any unauthorized and unlicensed use.
Users are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the website, including, without limitation:
i. accessing data not intended for such user or logging into a server or account which the user is not authorized to access;
ii. attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorization;
iii. attempting to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including, without limitation, via means of submitting a virus to the Site, or other acts such as "overloading" or "flooding";
iv. sending unsolicited e-mail, including promotions and/or advertising of products or services;
Violation of these Security Rules may result in civil or criminal liability. The administration will investigate occurrences which may involve such violations and may involve, and cooperate with, law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who are involved in such violations.
Materials
As an Employer/Recruiter you represent, warrant and agree that all materials provided by you for use in connections with any job postings or company postings will not violate any laws or regulations. You warrant and agree that those materials will not violate any other person or companies copyright, trademark or incite any public or private action. You hereby grant DocCafe.Com, LLC a non-exclusive, royalty free license to any posted materials and to hyper link to such materials while you are a member of the site in good standing.
It is agreed that the Database is an asset. Database access is for the purpose of finding candidates that fill your current directly contracted job openings. Removing data from this database and using it for another purpose is in violation of this policy and you agree is an act of conversion. Conversion and continued use or sale of that information is a direct violation of this agreement and shall result in removal from the site and an assessment of monetary damages and if needed injunctive relief.
License to Use by Users who are Resource Writers, Posters and Commentors
DocCafe.Com, LLC hereby grants you a nonexclusive, limited, terminable, right to access and post on the sites for your professional purpose or the professional development of others as well as comments and personal and professional opinions. You may not sell, transfer or assign any of the Service or your rights to any of the Services provided to any third party without the express written authority of DocCafe.Com, LLC. You agree that you are solely responsible for any material that you post or upload to the site and any consequences arising from such posting. DocCafe.com LLC reserves the right to terminate your license at any time in the event that it determines that you are in breach of these Terms and Conditions. DocCafe.Com, LLC reserves the right to assess monetary damages for any unauthorized and unlicensed use. All License users in this section must agree and comply with the Terms of Use.
Banner and Third Party Sites: Our site has banners and links to third party web sites. We do not control, endorse or guarantee any content found on any site that is not owned and operated exclusively by Us. You further agree that this site/company will not be liable for any loss or damage of any sort associated with your use of third party sites or their content.
Site Security
We reserve the right to view, monitor and record any and all activity that occurs on the Site. This is done in order to preserve the integrity of the site and protect the users of the Site. Any actual or attempted unauthorized use of the site can result in removal from the site, damages, civil suits and/or criminal prosecution. We will release any information requested through a court order or subpoena regarding investigations and/or prosecutions.
Services
We reserve the right to change and/or discontinue any or all of its services at any time and for any reason. We also reserve the right to deny you access to the Site. You agree that you are over the age of 18 or the age of majority.
Termination of Services
This Site receives payment via credit card. In the event that you wish to cancel a service, written notice to us of such cancellation needs to be provided at least 3 business days prior to the renewal date, or credit card charge date, to avoid the next monthly charge. Any refunds issued will include a $20 service charge.
Partner Corporation
We have the right to partner with other public and private corporations. A partner corporation may contact you to obtain additional information regarding your opportunity or search and to provide you with assistance in your search. A partner corporation is required to comply with our privacy policy and is restricted from selling or distributing your information without your consent.
Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless this Site/Company, its' employees, stockholders, attorneys, agents and contractors against all claims, expenses, liabilities, losses, costs and damages, including reasonable attorney's fees, that the above stated agents, attorneys, employees, stockholders, contractors or entity may incur in connection with your use of the Site, any link or banner associated with the Site or any content you supply to or remove from the site.
Limits of Liability
This site/Company is not liable for any loss resulting from, but not limited to, failure of electronic or mechanical equipment, communication lines, telephone lines, other internet technology failure, database failure, computer viruses, unauthorized access, theft, natural disasters or federal regulation restrictions. We do not guarantee that the information provided or posted is free of technical, typographical or material content errors.
Responsibility
DocCafe.Com, LLC assumes no responsibility for documents, articles or materials posted by Users or their actions and representations on the site. DocCafe.Com, LLC acts as a portal for employment opportunities and professional information and does not accept responsibility for the contents or representation of posters or users. DocCafe.Com, LLC will in good faith investigate and attempt to resolve any reported misuse or abuse of the site reported by any User.
Applicable Law
All matters relating to your access to and use of the Site shall be governed by U.S. Federal law or the laws of the State of Wisconsin where the home office of this company is located. By agreeing to this Terms of Use Agreement, you agree to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and to the exclusive venue of the state courts of Wisconsin. In the event that the subject of the litigation is a Federal law question and requires resolution in a Federal forum you submit to the federal jurisdiction of the United States District Court for the Central District of Wisconsin. The parties shall first attempt to resolve the disputed issue through mediation prior to any court filings.
Severability- Entire Agreement
If a court rules that any provision of this agreement is unenforceable, the balance of this contract shall remain enforceable and the parties will ask the court to modify the unenforceable part if possible so that the paragraph and/or terms used becomes enforceable to the maximum extent allowable. Failure to enforce any specific provision of this agreement does not result in a waiver to enforcement of the remaining provisions.
Entire Understanding
This agreement, its restrictions and conditions constitute the entire agreement between this site/company and the user in terms of your use to this web site for searching and posting purposes. In the event, you subscribe to this site you may be subject to an additional agreement that governs among other items, distribution of jobs and information, the payment procedure and time periods of such subscription or advertisement. In that situation that agreement is an additional agreement that is entered into and the terms of that agreement stand and are represented independently from this stated agreement. In the event that there are conflicting terms in the two agreements regarding the use of this site, the terms of the additional separate agreement shall be controlling.
Privacy Policy
We welcome you to DocCafe.Com, LLC! We want you to be aware of our privacy policy, because privacy policies are not all alike.
Our company respects your individual privacy. Our privacy policy informs you of how we electronically collect and process your information. This policy will inform you of options that you have to control or restrict the availability and use of your information.
DocCafe.Com, LLC ("DocCafe.com", "DocCafe.Com, LLC", "DocCafe.com", "us", "we", or "our") is a limited liability company registered in the state of Indiana in the United States of America with its principal office in Warsaw, Indiana. We provide users, ("user/s", "you", "your") services delivered via DocCafe.Com, LLC website, a mobile application, .mobi site and/or any other platform or media thorough which we make our services available. A "user" may be a member, a visitor, an affiliate, a partner, company, partner site, poster, writer or any other person or company that participates in a DocCafe.Com, LLC service.
Consent
Each time you use this site or provide us with information you represent that you agree to the terms of this policy. When you submit data to this site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with the terms of this policy as outlined and discussed below.
Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it. You agree that by using these sites you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described herein.
Terms
Important terms in this policy are, "personally identifying information", "non-identifying information" and "server data". This Privacy Policy incorporates by reference the Terms and Conditions for the sites which apply to this privacy policy.
How we get to know our customers
We are in the business of putting people in touch with other people. That requires more than innovative technical services. It requires that we understand you and your needs. We get to know you primarily through information that you provide to us when registering and using our site. The information that you provide ranges from basic contact information to payment information, to technical IP file information. When you register with our site you agree to provide and maintain accurate, complete and updated information. You further agree to our use of your information consistent with this Privacy Policy and the laws of the United States.
For operational and quality assurance purposes, we keep track of site traffic patterns and maintain log files of user access to site files. The information that we receive from or about you is stored on a system that is designed to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alternation or destruction of that information. We also use an outside provider that encrypts your sensitive information such as credit card numbers to ensure your privacy. We collect information to better understand our market and to better serve you.
We use the above collected information to monitor and improve our internal operations. We also use it to ensure that we bill you correctly, administer your account accurately and that we properly perform the services of this site. We use the collected information to improve the users experience with the site. The data helps us to determine how much our customers use certain parts of the site, allowing us to enhance those parts to fit the needs of the users. You agree the DocCafe.Com, LLC can use your provided information to contact you and to deliver information to you that is targeted to your interests or for administrative or partner driven purposes. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive information from our sites and partners. If you do not wish to receive this information you may opt out of any further promotional or job related emails but will remain on the list for administrative purposes. DocCafe.Com, LLC may also use non identifiable information about its users to prepare demographic analysis and reports.
Personally Identifiable Information
When you register with us your name, address, etc. is recorded in our database. This information is not for sale or use by anyone except our company and its network of job board sites, our partner corporations and our subcontractors. We do contract with other companies to assist us in our abilities to better serve you. Those companies will have access to our database files and must comply with our strict privacy policy.
You may change, update or delete all of your personal information from this site at any time. Information that you have posted may have been recorded by users and then becomes their property. This may result in unsolicited messages from those third parties for which DocCafe.Com, LLC is not liable. In certain circumstances, you may have clicked through to the DocCafe.Com, LLC site through another website, in the event that you provided any information to that linked website prior to arriving onto the DocCafe.Com, LLC site, we are not liable for the use of that information. Wherever you reside or from whichever country you are using the services and/or submit information, you consent to our use of your information consistent with this Privacy Policy, in the United States.
We can make no claim or take any responsibility as to how your posted information is utilized by those that take if from the posting portion of this site. If you choose to post your information to be open to employers or recruiters and to be public on the web sites, those employers or recruiters users may access your information and place it in their own company data file. Once your information has been removed from the DocCafe.Com, LLC website and placed in an employer or recruiter company file, DocCafe.Com, LLC is not able to access or assist in any removal from those outside company files. DocCafe.Com, LLC is also not responsible for any use or sale of such information from that point. DocCafe.Com, LLC does offer users a privacy setting that assures only a limited amount of identifying information can be obtained through the DocCafe.com site. Please see Posted CV's and/or Positions on additional limitations regarding limiting identifying information.
Registration
In order to post on our site you will be required to complete a registration. This registration will request specific personal information about you, your firm, agency or hospital group. Contact information is required as a part of this registration. This information is used to contact the user of this site about services, changes in services as well as for billing needs. Information you provide that you request to be kept confidential will not show up on a public profile or posting. An option of confidential may limit your ability to post on some areas of the web site.
Posted CV's and/or Positions
Our subscribers, recruiters and employers view posted CV's and position postings. You may have us disclose as much personal information as you wish. You may want to consider what information you wish to be posted depending on whether your job search is common knowledge to your colleagues, current employer or staff. That is why this site allows you to identify what information you provide that you do not wish to appear in your public posting. It is our intention that only paying customers or prospective customers will have access to the CV or resume database, but we cannot guarantee that other parties will not without our consent gain access to the CV or resume database. Be aware that when you post personal information in an uploaded CV or resume, DocCafe.Com, LLC is not able to keep that information confidential. You may have marked your profile as confidential, but are providing identifying information through your uploaded CV or resume. We are not responsible for the use of any information in an uploaded CV's, resume or job posting taken from this site by a third party. We are also not responsible for the accuracy of any information uploaded or posted to the web site by a user. Any inappropriate information displayed in a CV or resume will be removed and all privileges of site use will be suspended.
Our goal is to provide a service that connects candidates with their desired position and location. It is also to assist employers and/or recruiters in finding the right candidate. We also provide professional information to users of the site to review, comment and contribute. Users of this site may copy or retain information to their files that you have posted. Although we attempt to hold our users to a high ethical standard, we are not responsible for their use of that information.
By posting on this site you represent to us that you have obtained consent from any third party individuals or business entities to post data regarding their specific job search or position posting. By posting information you also state that you have informed any third party of how they may access to view the information posted and how to contact you to rectify an inappropriate, incorrect or any unconsented to information.
No member or agents of this site/company shall be held responsible for the content or another member's posted information.
Fraudulent Access or Use
No company or user of this site shall provide another person or company with their password or access without our written consent. Any unauthorized access or use is an act of fraud and shall result in removal from the site and an assessment of reasonable charges for such fraudulent use. Reasonable charges shall be assessed based on each individual case. Fraudulent use results in damages and agreement to these terms, reflects your agreement to these terms of damages.
It is agreed that the Database is an asset. Database access is for the purpose of finding candidates that fill your current contracted job openings. Removing data from this database and using it for another purpose is in violation of this policy and you agree is an act of conversion. Conversion and continued use or sale of that information is a direct violation of this agreement and shall result in removal from the site and an assessment of monetary damages and if needed injunctive relief.
Email and online fraud are ongoing concerns for all internet businesses. If you are the recipient of an email that appears to come from DocCafe.Com, LLC and is a phishing email, spam or presents a position that seems too good to be true, please contact us so we can follow up on it immediately. If you are asked for your log in information or any other personal information, please do not provide it and again, contact us immediately. We will take immediate action.
E-Mail
All initial correspondence will be through an e-mail message directed from our site. This allows recruiters and employers to establish direct contact with you without revealing your name or identifying information. Once you have received a request for further interest in your CV or posted position through that initial e-mail message, you may choose to correspond directly with the individual or group. Responding directly to that initial email may result in that recruiter or employer obtaining identifying information directly from your response. DocCafe.Com, LLC is not responsible for any information released directly by you in response to correspondence you receive from the web site. If you do not blind your CV or apply directly to a position via the site, you are responsible for any information provided to that subscriber, recruiter, employer or candidate in any correspondence. We do not have any control regarding the information you provide to third parties you come into contact from our site.
You will also be notified automatically of any job opportunities that match your specialty or geographic preferences. You may choose when and if you want to respond to those opportunities.
Linking to other Sites
You may access other sites through advertisements on this website as well as resource links provided. Once you leave this site, our privacy policy, as well as the other policies in effect on this site, will no longer be in effect. You will become subject to that site's policies. Make sure that you read their policies before proceeding.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files recorded in a user's hard drive. Cookies are used by many sites to help track user information and to assist with password identification and in remembering a user making multiple trips to the Web site. Cookies do not damage user files and they cannot provide information from a user's hard drive. They simply allow us to provide a faster service and more personalized visit to our site. Our third party advertisers may also utilize cookies when you visit their site. This allows them to measure advertising effectiveness. This information is not personally identifiable. Most internet browsers allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning prior to a cookie being stored. Please be aware that failure to allow a cookie to be placed on your computer may result in certain features or services failing to function properly.
We may use third party advertising companies which may place or access cookies on your computer. This information is used to provide information about goods and services of interest to you or to tailor demographic or preference information so we can better serve you.
Security
This Site uses a variety of programs to protect user's information. Information such as credit card numbers are encrypted and protected using one of the best encryption programs on the Internet. Information is backed up on a daily basis.
Notification of Changes
Please check back to this privacy policy on a regular basis. We reserve the right to change or modify this policy at any time. In the event that we change our policy, we will post a notification of change on the home page for thirty (30) days. In the event that you do not log into this site during that thirty (30) day period it is the users' responsibility to check the policy page for updated policy. You may opt out of any changes in the policy by notifying us with an e-mail to our contact e-mail address. In the event that you do wish to opt out, the previous privacy policy in effect at the time that you made payment will be in effect for the remainder of the period that has been prepaid. The user at that time can determine whether they wish to discontinue their use of this site's services or if they wish to continue using the site under the changed policy provisions.
Employee Accountability
Only the employees of this site/company, it's contractors or partner corporation employees that have a legitimate business purpose for accessing and handling personal information obtained on this site are given authorization to do so. Our information management system is set up so that all unauthorized employees are blocked from being able to obtain confidential or sensitive information.
U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S. Swiss Safe Harbor Framework
DocCafe.Com, LLC complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S. Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. DocCafe.Com, LLC has certified that it adheres to the Safe harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. Information is located at http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. Please feel free to contact us with any questions.
Compliance with the Us-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, we will resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection and use of your personal information. Any concerns or complaints please contact us. Unresolved privacy issues under the U.S. EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles will be referred for independent dispute resolution.
DocCafe.Com, LLC cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy. We are committed to protecting your privacy but in some circumstances we are not able to control the actions of others that may result in your information becoming public. As a user of this site, you understand and agree that you are assuming responsibility and risk associated with the placement of personally identifiable information on this web site either directly or by uploading documents to this web site, direct use and actions and conduct on and off of this site.
Do Not Do's
This is a list of things that this site does not do. It is by no means a comprehensive listing but is one that is created to ensure your private information remains private unless you decide otherwise:
We do not sell names of job seekers.
We do not post personal information that is requested to be kept confidential.
We will not identify a job seeker to a recruiter or employer without your prior approval.
We enforce a zero Spam policy.
We do not intentionally or knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18 that visit this site.
Please do not give your social security number to anyone that contacts you.
Never give out a credit card or bank account number to a prospective employer/recruiter.
Be careful what personal information you provide to people that you do not know.
Responsibility
The user accepts all risks and responsibility.
Contact Us
In the event that you have any questions please feel free to contact us at contact@doccafe.com, or by letter at DocCafe.Com, LLC, in 224965 Star Dust Lane
Ringle, WI 54471
United States. Please include your name and address in all correspondence.
Job Posting Guidelines
We maintain strict quality assurance policies for our database of jobs. To post jobs on our website, they must meet the following guidelines.
By posting on this site you represent to us that you are posting job data for positions that you have a direct contract for or that you represent directly. You are not allowed to post job data on behalf of a consortium, job network, data aggregation service, search engine, or other entity not directly responsible for the position in question. All job posters much have obtained consent from any/all business entities to post data regarding their specific job search or position posting. By posting information you also state that you have informed any third party of how they may access to view the information posted and how to contact you to rectify any inappropriate or incorrect information. Any job poster and/or their company violating this policy will be banned from the site and/or have their IP address banned.
The DocCafe.Com, LLC database is a valued asset. By using the DocCafe.Com, LLC site you acknowledge and agree to such. In the event that your company and employees have access to the DocCafe.Com, LLC database, you agree that the use of the database will be for the sole purpose of sourcing candidates for current contracted positions. Any other use MUST be disclosed in writing to the company and approved in writing. Failure to obtain approval results in conversion of valued information under the condition of fraud and misrepresentation and may be actionable in a court of law.
The following data guidelines apply to all jobs posted on DocCafe.com:
Your jobs must include complete titles, descriptions, locations and company information.
You should not post the same job repeatedly. Only 1 posting is allowed per job position.
Your jobs must not be commission only positions.
A valid contact e-mail address must be supplied for each job. We do not allow external URLs to be used for the application process. We will push applicants to an approved ATS system or an API will be available for your use.
Job Feeds must be in an industry standard format or in a proprietary format provided by you to us or jobs can be provided via an excel spreadsheet. We provide the necessary documentation.
Jobs must be kept updated and all filled positions removed from the site within 48 hours.
Job postings shall comply with all federal antidiscrimination laws.
Failure to comply with these guidelines will result in your jobs being removed from DocCafe.com and in some cases, at the sole discretion of our staff, your account will be suspended.
